# Zenia Gist

Open to relocating fi

918.640.7967

zeniagist@gmail.com

https://linkedin.com/in/zeniagist in

https://zeniagist.github.io #

Accounting specialist turned web developer with highly developed problem-solving and time management skills. Skilled at identifying solutions to stay within the projected budget and ensure deadlines are met. Key project involved forecasting budget needs through analyzing past trends in customer retention, payroll, and advertising.

#### **Skills**

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, HTML, CSS,

ISON

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React Native,

Angular, Express, Bootstrap, jQuery

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

Other: Heroku, Git, Bash, Microsoft Office Suite

# **Projects**

#### Event Meetup / https://zeniagist.github.io/eventmeetup/

**JUNE 2021** 

React, NodeJS, Gherkin, Google Calendar API, AWS, HTML, CSS

Serverless PWA using Google Calendar API to fetch upcoming events where users can search for a city and view a list of events hosted in the selected city.

### Chatterbox / https://github.com/zeniagist/chatterbox

MAY 2021

React Native, Firebase, Expo, Gifted Chat, Android Studio, HTML, CSS

Native mobile chat app that allows users to send pictures and location online or offline stored locally with Google Firestore

### filmFlix / https://zeniagist.github.io/filmflix/

APRII, 2021

Angular, TypeScript, Node.JS, Express, MongoDB, Passport, HTML, CSS

Provides users with the access to information about different movies, directors and genres. Users are able to sign up, update personal information, and create a list of their favorite movies.

# Experience

JULY 2020 – PRESENT

JANUARY 2016 – JUNE 2018

## Accounting Specialist / HireCall/Trak-1 Technology - Tulsa, OK

Facilitated company's return budget by meeting with department heads to understand the best method to receive budget reports to fit their needs. The result was the increased use of reports and faster decision-making attention variances.

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2020

### Outbound Client Engagement Specialist / Peoplefacts - Tulsa, OK

Quality check of all criminal background screens for accuracy and turnaround time. Identified criminal searches which were past the county or state determined turnaround time and investigated the reasoning

#### **Education**

**JUNE 2021** 

Full-Stack Immersion Certificate / CareerFoundry - Online Bootcamp

**MAY 2020** 

AS in Computer Information Systems / Tulsa Community College – Tulsa, OK